Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids: Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：是的，是的，队长。
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants. ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤。 ♪
Captioning provided by
MTV Networks
字幕提供者
MTV网络
May I help you?
我可以帮你吗？
Well...
出色地...
it's almost quittin'
time, Squidward.
几乎要放弃了
时间到了，章鱼哥。
Got any big plans
for after work?
有什么大计划吗
下班后？
Nope.
没有。
: Grr...
: 呃...
Hey, Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
Pretty incredible
shift, huh?
相当不可思议
换班吧？
If you say so.
如果你这么说的话。
Any plans after work?
下班后有什么计划吗？
No.
不。
Yeah, me neither.
是的，我也一样。
Just gonna be hangin'
at  "Casa de Sponge".
只是会挂着
在“海绵之家”。
Feel free to drop by if
you're in the neighborhood.
如果有的话请随时过来
你就在附近。
Hey Squidward, wait up.
嘿，章鱼哥，等一下。
Squidward, I realize
that I didn't really extend
章鱼哥我明白了
我并没有真正扩展
a proper invitation
back there.
适当的邀请
回到那里。
So what do
ya say, Squidward?
那怎么办
你说，章鱼哥？
How 'bout you come over to my
house for a visit tonight?
你到我这里来怎么样？
今晚要去看望房子吗？
Squidward, Squidward?
章鱼哥，章鱼哥？
SpongeBob, thank you so much
海绵宝宝，非常感谢你
for that lovely invitation
为了那个可爱的邀请
but I must
respectfully tell you
但我必须
恭敬地告诉你
I will never visit you.
我永远不会拜访你。
Ever!
曾经！
Take heart, Squidward.
振作起来，章鱼哥。
It'll all be over soon.
一切很快就会结束。
: Ohh...
: 哦...
Please  come over
for a visit, Squidward.
请过来
来拜访，章鱼哥。
It's been so long.
已经过去这么久了。
I can't even remember
your last visit.
我什至不记得了
您上次来访。
That's probably because
I've never visited you.
这可能是因为
我从来没有拜访过你。
: Please,
please, please...
: 拜托，
拜托，拜托……
Please!
请！
Please...
请...
Please?
请？
Please, please-please...
拜托，拜托，拜托……
Please, please-please.
拜托，拜托，拜托。
: Please...
： 请...
Please... Please.
拜托...拜托。
OK, Squidward,
maybe some other time.
好的，章鱼哥，
也许其他时间。
French man: 24 hours later.
法国人：24小时后。
Hey-o Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
You got any...
你有什么...
Before you ask me
that question
在你问我之前
那个问题
ask yourself this:
问问自己：
Why would I leave
the comfort of  my  home
我为什么要离开
我家的舒适
what if I got a couple
for  your  dirty of throw pillows?
如果我有一对怎么办
为你肮脏的抱枕？
Patrick, has Squidward
ever visited you at home?
帕特里克有章鱼哥
曾经拜访过你家吗？
Only once.
只有一次。
To take back some
stuff I borrowed.
去拿回一些
我借的东西。
He said he wouldn't leave
the comfort of his own home
他说他不会离开
自己家的舒适感
for my dirty little hovel.
为了我肮脏的小茅屋。
Borrow something,
then he'll have to come
over to get it back.
借东西，
那么他就必须来
过去把它拿回来。
Ah!
啊!
Well... Hey, thanks for letting
me play puzzle with you.
嗯...嘿，谢谢你让
我和你一起玩拼图。
See ya later.
稍后见。
That's it.
就是这样。
Squidward: A stick of butter
章鱼哥：一块黄油
and just a touch of pepper.
和一点胡椒粉。
Gah!
嘎！
Not on the rug.
不在地毯上。
: Oh.
： 哦。
SpongeBob, will
you keep it down?
海绵宝宝，会
你把它记下来吗？
I am trying to cook.
我正在尝试做饭。
Oh hey, Squidward.
哦嘿，章鱼哥。
Just doing a little
home improvement.
只做一点点
家居装修。
Well, you made me
spill pepper all over
my imported rug.
好吧，是你让我
把胡椒洒得到处都是
我的进口地毯。
:
OK, Squidward.
：
好的，章鱼哥。
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Need the right tool for the job.
需要适合这项工作的工具。
Huh?
啊？
SpongeBob: "Dear Squidward...
海绵宝宝：“亲爱的章鱼哥……
Thanks for lending me
your vacuum cleaner.
谢谢你借给我
你的吸尘器。
Sincerely,
SpongeBob SquarePants."
真诚的，
海绵宝宝。”
Oh, P.S.
哦，附注
: Bah...
: 呸...
Bah...
呸...
SquarePants residence.
方裤住宅。
Why do you have
my vacuum cleaner?
为什么你有
我的吸尘器？
Squidward.
章鱼哥。
It's been quite a while
since I last got a call
已经有一段时间了
自从我上次接到电话以来
from my favorite
next door neighbor.
从我最喜欢的
隔壁邻居。
That's because
I've  never  called you.
那是因为
我从来没有给你打过电话。
Now, why have you stolen
my vacuum cleaner?
现在，你为什么要偷东西
我的吸尘器？
I didn't steal it, silly,
I borrowed it.
我又没偷，傻瓜
我借的。
Are you done cleaning up that
dingy hole you call home?
你清理完了吗
你称之为家的肮脏洞？
You won't even recognize
the place, Squidward  .
你甚至不会认出
这个地方，章鱼哥。
Yeah, probably not.
是的，可能不会。
I'll be over to get
my vacuum in 20 minutes.
我会过去得到
20分钟后我的吸尘器就完成了
Oh, Squidward is finally
coming for a visit.
哦，章鱼哥终于来了
前来参观。
:
Sassa frassin
mala pookin tarny rasser...
：
檫木
马拉普金塔尼雷瑟...
Squidward,
I've been expecting you.
章鱼哥，
我一直在等你。
Welcome to my humble abode.
欢迎来到我简陋的住所。
I hope that you
will find comfort
我希望你
会找到安慰
and please don't hesitate
to ask me if there's
anything that I can...
请不要犹豫
问我是否有
任何我能做的...
Yeah, uh-huh, I just want
my vacuum back...
是啊，嗯，我只是想要
我的真空吸尘器回来了...
You've made an exact
replica of my living room.
你已经做了一个精确的
我客厅的复制品。
Well, you said
you wouldn't leave
the comfort of your home.
嗯，你说
你不会离开
您家的舒适度。
So I brought
the comfort here.
所以我带了
这里的舒适度。
Isn't it great  ?
不是很好吗？
No, it isn't.
不，不是。
You can't just steal
my decorating style and...
你不能只是偷窃
我的装修风格和...
Never mind,
just give me my vacuum.
没关系，
把我的真空吸尘器给我吧。
Would you care for a cool
and refreshing iced tea?
你想要一个酷吗
和清爽的冰茶？
No.
不。
I don't even know
what that is.
我什至不知道
那是什么。
Please just give me my vacuum
so I can get back home.
请给我我的真空吸尘器
这样我就可以回家了。
I have a casserole
in the oven.
我有一个砂锅
在烤箱里。
Yes, of course.
是的当然。
Please, have a seat while
I go grab your vacuum.
请坐
我去拿你的真空吸尘器。
Please make yourself at home.
请别客气。
Enjoying your visit
so far, Squidward?
享受您的访问
到目前为止，章鱼哥？
This is not a visit.
这不是一次访问。
You are going
to get my vacuum.
你要去
得到我的真空吸尘器。
And stop fluffing
this pillow.
并停止起毛
这个枕头。
OK, Squidward.
好的，章鱼哥。
Just yell if you
need anything.
只要大喊一声，如果你
需要任何东西。
Imbecile...
蠢货...
How did he do it?
他是怎么做到的？
He got my coffee table,
my vase, snack bowl...
他拿走了我的咖啡桌，
我的花瓶、零食碗……
Coasters, and my "Art of the
Clarinet" coffee table book.
杯垫和我的“艺术”
单簧管”咖啡桌书。
And this pillow looks just like
the one mommy made for me.
这个枕头看起来就像
妈妈为我做的那个。
He even copied
her stitch signature.
他甚至抄袭
她的针迹签名。
"For Squiddy with love, Mama."
“妈妈，用爱献给鱿鱼。”
: Ahh!
：啊！
You yelled?
你喊了？
Never mind, I'll find
the vacuum myself.
没关系，我会找到的
我自己真空。
OK, make yourself at home.
好吧，别客气了。
Squidward sure seems to
be enjoying his visit.
章鱼哥确实似乎
很享受他的来访。
My hallway.
我的走廊。
Dear Neptune.
亲爱的海王星。
He even got the chip in
the paint from when I moved in.
他甚至还拿到了芯片
我搬进来时的油漆。
OK, Squiddy,
don't get creeped out.
好吧，鱿鱼，
别被吓到了。
Just get the vacuum and go home.
只需拿起真空吸尘器然后回家即可。
All right, isn't  this  neat?
好吧，这不是很整洁吗？
My bathroom.
我的浴室。
I have to give him
credit, though.
我必须给他
不过，信用。
Every detail is correct.
每个细节都是正确的。
How does he know the exact
contents of my medicine cabinet?
他怎么知道准确的
我的药柜里有什么？
My rash cream?
我的痱子膏呢？
That little sneak!
那个小鬼鬼祟祟的！
Did someone
say rash cream?
有人吗
说皮疹膏？
SpongeBob,
you idiot!
海绵宝宝，
你这个白痴！
Squidward, rash cream.
鱿鱼，皮疹膏。
Oops.
哎呀。
oh, no.
哦，不。
Aww...
哇...
Help!
帮助！
I don't think I have
a cream for that.
我不认为我有
一个奶油。
Oh, what a horrible nightmare.
哦，多么可怕的噩梦啊。
So are you enjoying your
stay at  "Chez Sponge?"
那么你享受你的
住在“海绵之家”？
Ahh...
啊...
Will you excuse me for a moment?
请原谅我一下好吗？
I need to use
the bathroom again.
我需要使用
又是浴室。
Hurry back,
Squidward.
快点回来，
章鱼哥。
I gotta find that vacuum
and get out of here.
我得找到那个真空
然后离开这里。
Ah!
啊!
He copied all 492
of my self-portraits.
他复制了全部 492 个
我的自画像。
And they're better than mine.
而且他们比我的更好。
He even got the rug right.
他甚至还把地毯铺好了。
Get a hold of yourself,
Squiddy, old bean.
把握好自己，
鱿鱼，老豆子。
This doesn't mean anything.
这没有任何意义。
This, this... all of
this is just, just...
这，这……全部
这只是，只是……
mimicry.
模仿。
He doesn't possess your style
他没有你的风格
or your decorating acumen
或者你的装饰天赋
or your love of
the finer things.
或你的爱
更精细的事情。
In fact, the only thing
he has is...
其实唯一的事情就是
他有的是...
is, is...
是、是...
my vacuum cleaner.
我的吸尘器。
And I'll remedy that
我会解决这个问题
...post-haste.
...急如星火。
Ah-ha.
啊哈。
He put you in here along
with all his bad taste.
他把你一起放在这里
和他所有的坏品味。
You're coming home  ...
你要回家了...
home... with me.
家……和我在一起。
: With me.
： 与我一起。
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Is it really you?
真的是你吗？
It  is  you.
是你。
Mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah.
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。
Come on, baby.
来吧，宝贝。
You and I will walk
out of this horror show
你和我将行走
从这部恐怖剧中
the way we walked into it:
我们走进它的方式：
with dignity and aplomb.
带着尊严和沉着。
My house.
我的房子。
You just missed
the fire.
你刚刚错过了
火。
What happened
to my house?
发生了什么
到我家吗？
Oh, some knucklehead left
a casserole in the oven.
哦，还剩下一些傻瓜
烤箱里的砂锅。
Sponge...
海绵...
...Bob!
...鲍勃！
Aw, don't worry, Squidward.
哦，别担心，章鱼哥。
You're more than welcome
to stay at my house
非常欢迎您
住在我家
until you get your house fixed.
直到你把房子修好。
Why yes, I'd love another
spot of tea, Mr. Vacuum Cleaner.
为什么是的，我会喜欢另一个
点茶，吸尘器先生。
Care for some casserole?
想要一些砂锅吗？
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
You OK?
你还好吗？
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
SpongeBob: Squidward!
海绵宝宝：章鱼哥！
Ahh...
啊...
Replica sweet replica.
复制品甜蜜的复制品。
It sure was great
having Squidward over
for a visit, ay, Gary?
确实很棒
章鱼哥过来
来拜访，嗯，加里？
Meow.
喵。
French man:  Ah, another quiet
day in Bikini Bottom.
法国男人：啊，又安静了
比基尼泳裤的一天。
But it wasn't always this way.
但情况并非总是如此。
Once it was horrible.
有一次真是太可怕了。
The unimaginable happened.
难以想象的事情发生了。
One day, SpongeBob SquarePants
有一天，海绵宝宝
changed his pants.
换了裤子。
I remember as if
it were yesterday.
我记得好像
那是昨天的事了。
But in fact,
it happened  three  days ago.
但事实上，
这件事发生在三天前。
It's laundry
day, Gary.
这是洗衣服
天，加里。
Oops.
哎呀。
Meow.
喵。
Now to finish the day's chores.
现在要完成一天的家务了。
Hello?
你好？
Hello, may I speak
with SpongeBob?
你好，我可以说话吗
和海绵宝宝？
Uh, uh...
呃，呃……
: Square...
： 正方形...
Pants?
裤子？
Mm, speaking.
嗯，说话了。
Hey, hey, you wanna hear
how long I could do this for?
嘿嘿嘿你想听吗
我可以这样做多久？
Blah-loo-blah-loo-blah-loo...
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦……
Blah-loo-bla-loo-bla-loo...
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦……
Actually, Patrick, I'm kind
of busy, can it wait?
事实上，帕特里克，我很友善
很忙，可以等吗？
Blah-loo-blah-loo-blah-loo...
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦……
No.
不。
Blah-loo-blah-loo...
巴拉-卢-巴拉-卢...
Much later.
很久以后。
Blah-loo-blah-loo-blah-loo...
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦……
Softly: Gary, go check on
轻声：Gary，去看看吧
Oh, meow.
哦，喵。
...blah-loo-blah-loo-blah-loo...
...巴拉-卢-巴拉-卢-巴拉-卢...
Much  much  later...
很久很久以后...
Uh, pretty long time, huh?
呃，很长一段时间吧？
Yeah, Patrick.
是的，帕特里克。
Gary?
加里？
They shrunk!
他们缩小了！
I'm gonna need to get new pants.
我需要买条新裤子。
Sales Clerk: I'm sorry,
Mr. SpongeBob,
but we're not expecting
售货员： 对不起，
海绵宝宝先生，
但我们并不期待
another shipment
of SquarePants for months.
另一批货物
SquarePants 长达数月之久。
Ohh...
哦...
No, nope.
不，不。
Ooh, not these.
哦，不是这些。
Unh-unh.
呃呃。
Whoa.
哇哦。
These pants hug my body
这条裤子拥抱我的身体
better than my own mother.
比我自己的母亲更好。
Hey, Patrick...
嘿，帕特里克...
Notice anything different?
注意到什么不同了吗？
Pose, pose, pose...
姿势，姿势，姿势……
...pose?
...姿势？
: Bah...
it's me, SpongeBob.
: 呸...
是我，海绵宝宝。
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
No you're not.
不，你不是。
SpongeBob has
square  pants.
海绵宝宝有
方裤。
Now leave me alone,
you mysterious stranger.
现在让我一个人呆着吧
你这个神秘的陌生人。
Patrick's so full
of tarter sauce.
帕特里克太饱了
塔塔酱。
I'm still me.
我还是我。
It's just a pair of pants.
这只是一条裤子。
It's not like my friends
won't recognize me.
这不像我的朋友们
不会认出我的。
Sandy: Well,
howdy, stranger.
桑迪：嗯，
你好，陌生人。
I don't recognize you in
those new-fangled dungarees.
我认不出你了
那些新奇的工装裤
You must be
SpongeBob Fancy Pants.
你一定是
海绵宝宝花式裤子。
Clothes really
do make the man.
衣服确实
做男人。
Sandy didn't
recognize me, either.
桑迪没有
也认得我。
These pants are more powerful
than I thought.
这条裤子更有力量
比我想象的要多。
'Course it was just sandy.
当然，那只是沙子。
And Neptune knows what goes on
inside a squirrel's head.
海王星知道发生了什么
在松鼠的脑袋里。
Eww... But I know my best buddy
Squidward will recognize me.
呃……但我认识我最好的朋友
章鱼哥会认出我的。
We have been through
so much together.
我们已经经历过
在一起这么多。
♪ La-la-la-la, la-la,
la-la, la-la, la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦，啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦啦♪
Oh, no.
哦，不。
It's that little
yellow freak.
就这么小
黄色怪物。
:
Hi, Squidward.
：
嗨，章鱼哥。
Just ignore him,
maybe he'll go away.
直接无视他就好了
也许他会走开。
:
Oh, Squidward.
：
哦，章鱼哥。
♪ Guess who? ♪
♪ 猜猜是谁？ ♪
Do I know you?
我知道你？
Oh, sure you do,
it's me.
哦，当然你知道，
是我。
SpongeBob... SquarePants?
海绵宝宝...方裤？
Never seen you
before in my life.
从未见过你
以前在我的生活中。
Ooh.
哦。
Well, maybe these pictures of us
together will jog your memory.
好吧，也许我们的这些照片
在一起会唤起你的记忆。
Me and you at my birthday party.
我和你在我的生日聚会上。
You and me at work.
你和我在工作。
That little slumber party
we had last week.
那个小小的睡衣派对
我们上周有过。
I forgot when this was taken.
我忘记了这是啥时候拍的。
Is that supposed
to be you?
是这样认为的吗
成为你？
I can't believe it.
我简直不敢相信。
He actually left.
他确实离开了。
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
呼呼呼！
It's like we'd never met.
就好像我们从未见过一样。
Maybe Patrick is right.
也许帕特里克是对的。
Oh, no, it's locked.
哦，不，它被锁了。
Gary, hey Gary.
加里，嘿加里。
Can you open the door?
你能开门吗？
I left my keys
in my other pants.
我留下了钥匙
在我的另一条裤子里。
Hello?
你好？
Can I help you?
我可以帮你吗？
Patrick, it's me, SpongeBob.
帕特里克，是我，海绵宝宝。
Oh, right, you're that
Round Pants fellow.
噢，对了，你就是那个
圆裤的家伙。
Patrick, what are you
doing in my house?
帕特里克，你是什么？
在我家做什么？
Your house?
你家？
This house belongs
to SpongeBob SquarePants.
这房子属于
海绵宝宝。
At least it did
before he left us.
至少它做到了
在他离开我们之前。
I wish I could see him
one last time.
我希望我能见到他
最后一次。
Oh, barnacles.
哦，藤壶。
I guess I'm not SpongeBob
SquarePants anymore.
我想我不是海绵宝宝
不再是四角裤了。
I'll have to start
all over again.
我必须开始
一切重新来过。
...Hello, sir, I'd like
an application, please.
...您好，先生，我想要
请提交一份申请。
My name is SpongeBob
square... Ahh.
我的名字是海绵宝宝
方形...啊。
Oh, whoo, hm.
哦，呼，嗯。
Sorry, I'm a little
对不起，我有点
I'm a little...
Sorry, I'm a little nervous.
我有点...
抱歉，我有点紧张。
My name is SpongeBob
Round...  Pants.
我的名字是海绵宝宝
圆形...裤子。
And I would like
to seek employment from
this eating establishment.
我想要
寻求就业
这家餐饮场所。
Oh, dear, are you OK,
Mr. Cashier... Ooh!
噢，亲爱的，你还好吗，
收银员先生...哦！
Here are the applications.
以下是应用程序。
Let's see here.
让我们看看这里。
Name: SpongeBob RoundPants.
名称：海绵宝宝圆裤。
Well, this is going well.
嗯，一切进展顺利。
Hey, Mr. Cashier,
looks like we're gonna be
嘿，收银员先生，
看起来我们会
co-workers!
同事们！
Question two: "Have you ever
been convicted of a felony?"
问题二：“你有没有
被判重罪了吗？”
Hm, what's a felony?
嗯，什么是重罪？
Being too darn happy
all the time.
太幸福了
一直。
Oh, yeah, lots and
lots of felonies.
哦，是的，很多
很多重罪。
Heh, moron.
呵呵，白痴。
What's going on here?
这是怎么回事？
I'm filling out
an application.
我正在填写
一个应用程序。
Get to work.
开始工作吧。
I got the job?
我得到了这份工作吗？
Oh, boy.
哦，男孩。
My first day
on the job.
我的第一天
在工作中。
I am so excited.
我很兴奋。
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
Whatever.
任何。
You've worked here a long time.
你在这里工作了很长时间了。
Why don't you show
this rookie the ropes.
你为什么不显示
这个菜鸟绳索。
Oh, I'd love to.
哦，我很愿意。
Yay!
耶！
What, no, don't...
什么，不，不要...
So what do I do first?
那么我首先要做什么？
: Fine.
： 美好的。
Take a Krabby Patty
and put it on the grill.
吃一个蟹肉饼
然后把它放在烤架上。
Shouldn't you watch it?
难道你不应该看吗？
Why, I don't think
it's going anywhere.
为什么，我不认为
它会去任何地方。
Ooh, very Zen.
哦，很有禅意。
What next, oh, oracle
of Krabby wisdom?
接下来呢，哦，神谕
蟹蟹的智慧？
I'm going to the bathroom.
我要去趟洗手间。
Hm, I'll go too.
嗯，我也去。
How's it going in there, boss?
老板，里面怎么样？
Um... Fine.
嗯……好吧。
"Going fine."
“一切顺利。”
Oh,
Mr. Squidward?
哦，
章鱼哥先生？
What's you reading?
你在读什么？
"Bathroom break", check.
“上厕所休息”，检查一下。
Here's the slop
you ordered... Enjoy.
这是斜坡
您订购了...享受吧。
If you can choke it down.
如果你能把它压下去的话。
: Ha, ha-ha-ha.
: 哈哈哈哈。
"Be rude to customer
and insult food.
“对顾客无礼
并侮辱食物。
Nasally laugh."
笑得鼻青脸肿。”
Could I get
a Krabby Patty combo?
我可以得到
蟹肉饼组合？
No.
不。
How 'bout a double
Krabby Patty?
双人怎么样
克拉比·帕蒂？
Can I get a triple
patty with cheese?
我可以得到三份吗
奶酪馅饼？
Oh, I think you've had
way  too many of those.
哦，我想你已经有过
太多了。
Taught him
everything
he knows.
教他的
一切
他知道。
: Oh, ooh...
: 噢噢...
Customer: Come on.
顾客：来吧。
Customer:
Excuse me?
客户：
对不起？
What are
you two doing?
什么是
你们两个在做什么？
Get to work!
开始工作吧！
I'm used to Squidward
sleeping on the job
我已经习惯了章鱼哥
工作时睡觉
but I expect more
from you Mr. SquarePants.
但我期待更多
来自你方裤先生。
I am not SpongeBob SquarePants,
Mr. Krabs.
我不是海绵宝宝
蟹老板。
What in the name of Davy Jones
are you talking about?
以戴维·琼斯的名义
你在说什么？
I mean, do these pants
look square to you?
我是说，这条裤子
你觉得方形吗？
They're round.
它们是圆的。
Yeah, so?
是啊，所以？
I can't be SpongeBob SquarePants
with  round  pants.
我不能成为海绵宝宝
搭配圆裤。
Who told you that?
谁告诉你的？
Patrick.
帕特里克.
Well, why don't you
just take them off?
好吧，你为什么不
把它们脱掉就可以了吗？
Order up, Squidward.
下令吧，章鱼哥。
Well, well, if it isn't
好吧好吧，如果不是的话
SpongeBob UnderPants  .
海绵宝宝内裤。
Ahh!
啊！